import { Question } from "../contestantControls";

export const sethQuestions: Question[] = [
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "What Pokemon evolves into Sharpedo?",
    options: ["Carvanha", "Feebas", "Luvdisc"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "How many Pokemon are members of the Legendary Giants (As of Gen VI)?",
    options: ["5", "4", "3"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "What forest separates two parts of Route 104 in Pokemon Ruby/Sapphire?",
    options: ["Ilex Forest", "Petalburg Woods", "The roots of Rydel"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "In Pokemon Ruby/Sapphire what do you need to attach to Marill to produce an Azurill in the Day-care Centre?",
    options: ["Sea Foam", "Blue Incense", "Sea Incense"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "What is the name of the man who lets Pokemon learn forgotten moves?",
    options: ["Move Tutor", "Ancient Scholar", "Arcane Teacher"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: "Which Pokemon WON’T have Clear Body as an ability?",
    options: ["Metang", "Regirock", "Staryu"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "What’s the name of the legendary that is obtainable in Pokemon Black?",
    options: ["Reshiram", "Kyurem", "Zekrom"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: "How many Pokemon games were released on DSlite?",
    options: ["11", "18", "15"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "What is Victini’s gender?",
    options: ["Genderless", "Male", "Female"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: "Which Pokemon can be found in the Whirl Islands of Pokemon Heart Gold?",
    options: ["Celebi", "Lugia", "Mew"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: "What is the name of the world home to Giratina?",
    options: ["Mirror World", "Distortion World", "Torn World"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: "How many different forms does Rotom have?",
    options: ["6", "3", "5"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: "What pokemon does Tepig evolve into?",
    options: ["Grumpig", "Lechonk", "Pignite"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question: "Who is the Champion of the Pokemon League in Pokemon X/Y?",
    options: ["Cynthia", "Iris", "Diantha"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question: "Who is the Team Rocket leader in Pokemon Heart Gold/Soul Silver?",
    options: ["Giovanni", "Archer", "Jessie"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  }
];